[
{
"question": "HTML is what kind of language?",
"answers": {
"A": "markup",
"B": "markdown",
"C": "programming",
"D": "scripting",
"E": "idiomatic"
},
"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{
"question": "What does CSS stand for?",
"answers": {
"A": "Cute Syntax and Style",
"B": "Curly Styles and Sheets",
"C": "Cascading Style Sheets",
"D": "Cryptagraphically Secured Styles",
"E": "Cascading Syntax and Styles"
},
"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{
"question": "JavaScript is...",
"answers": {
"A": "a version of Java designed for scripting.",
"B": "is both a server side and client side language.",
"C": "not yet available on any version of Internet Explorer.",
"D": "what developed by Alan Turing.",
"E": "is the only programming language supported by all modern web browsers."
},
"correctAnswer": "BE"
},
{
"question": "PHP is a ...",
"answers": {
"A": "Client side language.",
"B": "Server side language.",
"C": "Design for building powerful websites",
"D": "Pre-Heated Python lexigrammer",
"E": "Proto-Hypertext Processing language"
},
"correctAnswer": "BC"
},
{
"question": "Python is a ...",
"answers": {
"A": "serpent based language.",
"B": "non-idiomatic, non-syntax language.",
"C": "is both a server-side and client-side language",
"D": "language with many libraries.",
"E": "shorter version of Anaconda."
},
"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{
"question": "Bash is not used for ...",
"answers": {
"A": "building websites.",
"B": "writing procedural code",
"C": "server-side scripting.",
"D": "handling simple tasks.",
"E": "uncompiled server directives."
},
"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{
"question": "MySQL is ...",
"answers": {
"A": "better than YourSQL.",
"B": "an Open Source Relational Database Management System.",
"C": "a proprietary JSON interpreter.",
"D": "stands for My Serverless Query Language.",
"E": "stands for My Super Quantum Language."
},
"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{
"question": "PostgreSQL is ...",
"answers": {
"A": "more popular than MySQL.",
"B": "not a Relational Database Management System.",
"C": "a popular Relational Database Management System.",
"D": "a web based programming language similar to Pascal",
"E": "a JSON based query language."
},
"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{
"question": "AJAX",
"answers": {
"A": "stands for Androgenous JavaScript and XML.",
"B": "impacts the DOM.",
"C": "is a JSON clenser.",
"D": "is an open-source language.",
"E": "uses javascript to communicate with a specific server"
},
"correctAnswer": "BE"
},
{
"question": "MEAN and LAMP",
"answers": {
"A": "are both web technology stacks.",
"B": "are asynchronous to each other.",
"C": "are the same.",
"D": "are two languages that don't require human coders",
"E": "are not web technologies."
},
"correctAnswer": "A"
}
]
